

Piriyapandh Thaisuriyo

Email: piriyapandh@gmail.com

Mobile: +66 81 907 3039

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am Thai woman, 47 years old (Born in 1968) with over 24 years of experience.

I am energetic, creative, realistic and work-result oriented.

My working style is hold on for accuracy rather than pleasant.

My straight are arranger, relator, focus, analytical and Input.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr 2015 – Present Head of PR & Communications (Vice President)

Evolution Capital PCL

Dec 2012 – Apr 2015 Senior Manager – Corporate Affairs (Public Relations)

Big C Supercenter PCL

Sep 1998 – Oct 2012 Corporate Public Relations Manager

King Power Group of Companies

Oct 1996 - Jun 1998 Marketing Communication Manager

Orient Thai Airlines

Sep 1994 – Sep 1996 PR & Advertising Manager

Golden Tour Bangkok LTD.

Dec 1990 – Aug 1994 Senior Reporter (Marketing Section)

Krungthepturakij Newspaper

Feb 1990 - Nov 1990 Guest Relations Officer

Royal Park Beach Resort, Phuket

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

| Thammasat University |
|---|
| MA in Mass Communication Administration with GPA 3.64 |
| Silpakorn University |
| BA in Liberal Arts (Thai/English) with GPA 2.51 |
| TriamUdom Suksa School |
| M6 in French/English |
| |

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Public Relations

Marketing Communication

KEY SKILLS AND

COMPETENCIES

Professional Abilities:

-PR & Communications

Strategic & Planning

- -Crisis Management
- -Problem Solving
- -Communicating with stakeholders
- -Media Relations

Managerial Abilities:

- -Work and People Management
- -Budget Control
- -Strategic Planning and Problem

Solving

-Negotiate

Hobbies & Interests:

- -Planting
- -Shopping
- -Travelling
- -Cultural Study

Computers Knowledge &

Languages:

- -Basic knowledge in MS Office
- -Good command in English & Thai

Reference: -upon request-

Home Address: 618/677 Lumpini

Park Pinklao, Boromarajonani Rd.,

Bangbamru, Bangplad, BKK 10700